Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Graham Parry from Citigroup.
Please go ahead.
Great. Thanks for taking my questions. So on telecast and a quick follow-up, as you just
issued, clarifies that 13 to 15% is what the trial is minimally powered to detect. I think you said
it was just what it was powered for, but I think the design paper says it's 20% on all comers.
And would you view that 13 to 15% as a clinically meaningful result? So that was a follow-up.
And then on REMI-MS, could you just comment on your confidence in achieving disability progression?
I was taught to the brain penetration of the molecule and action at the microglia compared
to remibrutinib, which actually didn't show that with statistical significance in its
phase three. Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Rob. So you are correct. 13 to 15 would mean a win. It's powered for
20% for the patients who are 70 milligrams in DL and above, or 25% for the 90 milligram
DL and above. And so I think we would say in the mid-teens, it's clinically meaningful,
given that these patients have no other option, and that this is an independent risk factor.
And so, yeah, we'll ultimately see what the data shows. And then with respect to REMI-MS,
I think we have everything that indicates to us that the trial has been conducted and
the data that we're seeing, that from an ARR standpoint, that we're on track versus
what we would have expected in the data set. As you know, with disability progression,
we have no way to know. And I think it's very difficult for me to handicap that. We
saw the data with remibrutinib. We do believe that our molecule is more potent on the target
and more selective. And so we're hopeful that that leads to the improvements in disability
progression that would bring us in line with the antibody-based B-cell therapies. But
there's no way for us to assess that in any sort of objective way at this point until
we study with that.
Thank you.
Our next question comes from the line of Rajesh Kumar from HSBC. Please go ahead.
One question for Mukul. Thanks for clarifying, you know, what sort of cost cut is flowing